An air kick turn?!
N-No way!
I-I did it!
I scored a point!
Are air kick turns that amazing?
It's one of the most difficult
moves to pull off in Flying Circus.
In order to use a mid-air
kick to change directions,
you need to have precise membrane control.
"Mem... brain"?
A layer of anti-gravity particles.
Even then, you normally wouldn't
see anyone do an air kick turn
using school Grav-Shoes.
Like a beginner using Li Men Ding Zhou?
This match is over!
The winner is Kurashina Asuka!
Coach! I won!
I won!
I don't really get all of it,
but Flying Circus is fun!
Congrats, Kurashina—
Thank you so much!
Kunahama Institute doesn't
have to lose its "In" now!
I graciously admit defeat.
That was awfully careless of me.
Satouin-san!
Wh-What is it?
Thank you for playing against me!
Well, you were all over the place,
but you're an amusing one.
Let's have a rematch sometime.
Sure!
May my wings be covered
in the blessings of blue.
Coach Hinata, thank you so—
Hinata-kun, was it?!
You have Flying Circus experience, don't you?
Your strategies and advice were on point!
Flying Circus experience?
No, not really.
It's just that Satouin-san moved
only forward and sideways,
so I thought that maybe she
was weak at vertical moves.
Wonderful!
It's good fortune that we met here!
No, it's destiny!
You all are destined to be the saviors
of the Kunahama Flying Circus team!
Let us work together from now o—
Oi!
Misaki-senpai...
Episode Two:
"Udon...?"
Senpai-Misaki...
How I miss you...
Misaki!
Senpai, Senpai!
Tobisawa
Good morning!
Morning, Mashiro-chan.
Thanks for always taking care of Misaki.
No problem!
Good morning.
I see you're starting another
day as Sleeping Beauty.
Wake up, Misaki-senpai.
Your udon's here.
Udon...?
Rise and shine.
You're a real handful every morning.
But I love that about you. too.
So sleepy...
We're off!
Have a nice day.
Why do we have to go to school every morning?
Senpai, you say that every day.
What's all this noise?
Good morning!
So she really can't stay
balanced without that posture.
Good grief.
I guess what happened yesterday
was just beginner's luck.
I heard all about it, Kurashina-san!
You actually scored a point against Satouin-san
from Takafuji Academy yesterday?
So the whole school already knows that
we protected Kunahama Institute's "In"?
"In"?
Beat the Champion, Shindou
Players Fired Up
Satouin Reiko & Ganeko Mayu
Beauties Soar the Sky
Anyway, Takafuji Academy is
a Flying Circus powerhouse,
and Satouin-san's their vice captain!
Wow, that's an awesome outfit!
It's a competition flying suit.
And you're what's awesome!
A total beginner scoring a
point against Satouin-san
is basically the upset of the century!
Like that match between the
United States and England!
The most shocking result
in World Cup history!
Thirty-six years since its pro leagues were
suspended, a USA team full of amateurs
beat England, which had racked
up an incredible 22-4 record!
How inspiring!
Oh, you can keep that magazine.
Thank you very much.
Do you play Flying Circus, Aoyagi-san?
Nah, I'm just support staff.
I only joined the team recently,
because my brother asked.
Since the seniors all graduated,
the only members left are the
captain—my brother—and me.
Please join, if you'd like.
Morning.
Good morning, Coach.
I heard all about your brilliant
job as second yesterday!
I didn't know you played FC, Hinata-kun.
I just played a little when I was a kid.
We'd love to have experienced players!
You should join our FC team, too—
I won't join.
Class is about to start, Aoyagi.
R-Right...
Eating tsuke udon outdoors is so pawesome!
The nukazuke pickles you
made are super-delish, too!
Here you go.
Registration Form
Flying Circus Team
Class 2-C
Kurashina Asuka
Wh-What's this?
I filled it out for you, so
all you gotta do is submit it.
That goes for you two, too.
Talk about covering all the bases.
Uh, I'm pretty sure this is forgery.
This actually looks a
lot like my handwriting.
Join now and get a free drink
at your welcome party!
What is this, a promotional campaign?
For real?!
You're like a hotshot scout, Aoyagi-senpai!
I'll join!
I'm no good at all, but I look
forward to working with you!
All right! Thank you, Kurashina-san!
Did the free drink seal the deal?
Please.
Join us, Misaki.
You used to play, didn't you?
Hmm... I don't meow.
There's no way she can
come to morning practice.
Also, she does things her own way,
so she can't handle the sports lifestyle.
Oh, I guess you're right.
Let's do it, Tobisawa-san!
Well, I'll consider it.
So, to remain healthy
throughout one's life...
Man...
And here I thought I had
no desire to go back.
Kurashina.
You're not hiding it very well.
I-I'm s-so...
...rry.
Welcome to the Flying Circus team!
Flying Circus Fan Club Team
Enter
Oh, good, you came!
R-Right...
What is it?
This is our club room?
That's right. Go on in.
Sorry it's so cramped.
Muscles are Life
Dammit, Bro, I told you
to clean this place up!
I didn't have time.
Whatever.
Huh, this is the club room?
Hey, Tobisawa-san!
And Arisaka-san!
What, am I not allowed to join?
Just so you know, wherever
Misaki-senpai goes,
I go with her.
We got three members at once!
I'm happy for you, bro.
All right! Practice starts tomorrow!
Sorry I'm late.
Good work on day duty.
What do you think, Masaya?
Kurashina, Tobisawa, and that first-year
Arisaka submitted registration forms.
The Kunahama FC team, which
had been reduced to a fan club,
just got three new members at once.
Did something happen?
Dunno.
I can't think of anything.
I see.
Um...
I don't have to be Kurashina-san's
instructor anymore, right?
I mean, she's joining the FC team.
Up to you.
I'm in your care, Coach!
I'm flying! I'm actually flying!
What happened to Coach Hinata?
Beats me.
Kurashina-san, I'm not your coach anymore.
What's wrong?
I told Kagami-sensei I wasn't needed anymore,
since you joined the FC team.
Is that so?
Okay!
Let's start practice!
Put your spirit into it!
First off, let's practice
flying from buoy to buoy.
Got it!
Good luck.
Guess I'll get off my tail for once.
A motivated Misaki-senpai?!
Going home, Masaya?
Yes.
Why don't you stay and watch?
It's been a while.
Wait for me, Misaki-senpai!
These newcomers have rather grim prospects.
They need to start with the very basics.
Run, train their core muscles,
and improve their reflexes.
Why don't you give them that advice, then?
I'm an outsider.
Misaki-senpai!
I-I can't...
N-No more...
My HP's been reduced to zero.
You lack spirit!
We won't be ready for the
summer tournament this way!
Well now. Today's their first day.
And we have to get them competition
Grav-Shoes and flying suits, too.
Yeah, yeah!
It's not fair that you're the only
one with a full set of equipment!
Sorry.
Tomorrow's Saturday, so how
'bout we all go shopping?
I'm in.
I haven't used my Grav-Shoes in ages,
so I'll have to get them tuned.
What about you, Kurashina-san?
I'll go!
And let's all take part
in the summer tournament!
I can't wait!
Then we need to show more spirit!
Okay!
Over here!
Good morning.
Morning.
Come this way.
Okay.
Wow, the ceiling's so high.
It's so people can take test flights.
Hello, Shirase-san.
Welcome.
Oh, Madoka-chan.
Not with your brother today?
I've brought the new members of the
Kunahama FC team with me today.
N-Nice to meet you!
I-Is that a guardian angel?
That's my little sister, Minamo.
Let's head to the second floor.
I'll pick out Grav-Shoes that suit you all.
Thanks.
Wh-Which type of Grav-Shoes?
The mannequin talked!
"Type"?
There are three types of Grav-Shoes: for
speeders, fighters, and all-rounders.
There are various styles of play that
each call for different shoes.
The speeder type, which specializes in
scoring points by touching the buoys faster.
The fighter type, which focuses in scoring
points by touching the opponent's back.
And the all-rounder type,
which is good at both.
These styles of play require Grav-Shoes
that emit membranes in different ways.
Oh, membranes.
Layers of anti-gravity particles, correct?
That's right.
Anti-Gravity
Grav-Shoes help you float
using anti-gravity particles,
and move using the Earth's gravitational field.
You know that much, right?
And they propel you forward and back
by adjusting the thickness of the membranes.
Speeder-type Grav-Shoes are calibrated
to obtain the highest top speed,
while fighter-types have lower
top speeds but improve agility.
You make things so easy
to understand, Senpai!
But I don't know which to choose.
I'm a complete beginner.
Th-Then I recommend you start
with the all-rounder type.
The shoes come with balancing tools,
which allow for fine-tuning.
Th-Thank you.
What type are you, Misaki-senpai?
Eh? I'm a fighter.
Then I'll go with fighter, too.
And I'll take this one.
Cute.
I've decided to appeal to
Misaki-senpai using cuteness.
Those are for speeders.
She's got her priorities all mixed up.
W-We'll calibrate it for fighter use.
Th-Thanks.
No go, huh?
Thank you.
Looks like the flying suits
will take about a month.
I can't wait!
By then, we'll have to be
good enough to play in matches.
Right.
I'm still no good at all.
Is that...
Could it be the re-release
version of "Downhill,"
the legendary electro-mechanical
arcade game?!
Well, I'll head home now.
Wait...
What's wrong?
Let's play!
Don't wanna. Sounds like a pain.
Those two sure are close.
Senpai!
They sure are.
Don't wanna. Sounds like a pain.
I'll be leaving, too, then.
See you Monday at school.
Join us, Kurashina-senpai!
I-I'm not much of a gamer, sorry.
Relax your waist, jeez.
I finally have competition Grav-Shoes!
Put your foot down, Kurashina.
Sorry.
Okay, let's practice with spirit—
Captain, I have a request.
What is it?
I want to have a match.
Oh, wow. Throwing yourself
to the wolves, huh?
With me?
No, with Kurashina-san.
Who, me?
Oh, that sounds good.
Show us your air kick turn again, Kurashina.
Wh-What?!
Let's zipzap together.
V-Very well.
Oh, a match?
Perfect timing, Sensei.
We need you as second.
Sure.
Actually...
Isn't there someone more suited than I am?
So sorry.
It's fine.
I won't do this again.
Hinata-san!
I'm in your care again!
S-Sure.
Tobisawa!
You ready?!
Too loud!
Er...
I have to either touch the
four buoys in sequence,
or touch your back, right?
Right.
But I won't let you touch
anything that easily.
I'll do my best!
Ready...
Set!
Not bad.
She said she was a fighter, but she's fast.
Point scored by Misaki! 1-0!
You're amazing, Misaki-senpai!
Kurashina-san!
Lean further forward!
Okay!
2-0!
At this rate, she'll get
the third point, as well.
Forget about the third point.
Take a shortcut!
Head right for the fourth line!
What's a shortcut, again?
Abandoning a buoy and getting to
the next line before your opponent.
Kurashina-san, shall we
give that move another go?
Point to Misaki! 3-0!
I understand.
Go!
Got it!
Is the air kick turn coming?
Open your legs wide to stop!
Gotcha!
Point to Misaki! 4-0!
That was a close shave. Nice, Misaki!
She still scored a point, though.
So it really was just beginner's luck.
One more!
Point to Misaki! 5-0!
I'm not done yet!
6-0!
It's as though Kurashina-senpai
has a bull's-eye on her back.
Too slow!
7-0!
8—
9-0!
Do whatever you can to lose her!
Change this momentum!
I'll at least score one point!
At least one point!
This match is over!
Tobisawa Misaki wins 9-0!
Are you okay?
I couldn't do the air kick turn,
and I couldn't score a single point.
I'm no good at all.
Misaki's got FC experience,
and you only just started—
I want to get good!
I want to get better!
Please be my coach again, Hinata-san!
I...
Are you gonna turn down such a cutie pie?
Come on, help her out.
Yeah.
How about at least until
the summer tournament?
I'm no good at all, but please teach me!
Fine.
As long as it's only till
the summer tournament.
Thank you! Thank you!
All's well that ends well, huh?
Yeah.
I'm not sure what this feeling
is, but it's not bad.
I fell for you all over again, Misaki-senpai.
You were like a cougar after its prey.
A cougar?
We'll have to celebrate your victory.
I'll treat you to an extra-large udon.
Udon...?!
Extra large!
Heh.
Hello? This is Kagami, from Kunahama High.
Let's hurry up and go!
Calm down, Senpai!
You're leaving already?
Yes. We've got more members now,
Bye-bye!
so if possible, we'd like the help
of Takafuji, the powerhouse school.
If you would be so kind,
we'd love to hold a joint
training camp with you.
To Be Continued
Preview
Wow, this is so exciting!
Of course the practice would be hardcore.
It's all good.
Episode Three:
"I Just Got a Little Fired Up"
I just got a little fired up.